Rosa Smith Eigenmann papers, 1870-1930 C59
Indiana University Archives
- Correspondence, 1870-1941, undated
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, July 11,1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann and Margaret Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, July 13, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann and Theodore Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, July 14, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann and Charlotte Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, July 16, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann and Charlotte Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, July 17, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann and Margaret Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, July 18, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, July 19, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, July 20, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, July 23, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann and Theodore Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, July 25, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, July 26, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann and Theodore Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, July 28, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann and Margaret Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, July 29-30, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, July 31, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Theodore and Adele Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, circa July 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, August 2-3, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, August 4-5, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, August 6, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Margaret, Theodore, and Adele Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, August 8, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, August 9, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann and Charlotte Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, August 10-11, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, August 13, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann, Charlotte, Theodore, and Adele Eigenmann (children) to Carl H. Eigenmann, August 14-16, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, August 17-18, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann, Margaret, Charlotte, and Theodore Eigenmann (children) to Carl H. Eigenmann, August 18-19, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, August 20, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, August 24, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, September 4-5, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, September 7, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, September 10, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, September 12, 1899 (Box 3)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, July 7-12, 1900 (Box 3)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, July 15, 1900 (Box 3)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, July 17, 1900 (Box 3)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, circa July 1900? (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Mary Smith Berry, August 2, 1900 (Box 3)
  - Etta(?) to "Grandmother", March 12, 1901 (Box 3)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, March 30, 1901 (Box 3)
  - Lucretia Smith to Elizabeth Easton Gray, January 30-February 2, 1902 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Adele Eigenmann, circa 1903(?) (Box 3)
  - Mary S. Berry to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, April 6, 1904 (Box 3)
  - Mary S. Berry to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, April 10, 1904 (Box 3)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, April 19, 1904 (Box 3)
  - Mary S. Berry to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, June 29, 1904 (Box 3)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Lucretia Smith ("Grandma"), December 23, 1904 (Box 3)
  - Philemon Woodruff to C.K. Smith, March 10, 1905 (Box 3)
  - Lucretia Smith to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, June 18, 1905 (Box 3)
  - E.R. Parry to "My dear little girl", June 19, 1905 (Box 3)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, September 10, 1905 (Box 3)
  - Louis P. Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, November 30, 1905 (Box 3)
  - Mary S. Berry to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, December 3, 1905 (Box 3)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, July 19, 1906 (Box 3)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, April 2, 1907 (Box 3)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, May 9, 1907 (Box 3)
  - John P. Eigenmann to "Paul", May 13, 1907 (Box 3)
  - Julia Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, May 30, 1907 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann and Charlotte Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, August 19, 1907 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, August 22, 1907 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, August 24, 1907 (Box 3)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, August 31, 1907 (Box 3)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, circa August 1907 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, September 2, 1907 (Box 3)
  - N.A. Young to J. Russell Smith, February 25, 1908 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Thora Eigenmann, March 22, 1908 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Ulysses H. Smith, December 28, 1908 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to children?, January 1, 1909 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Theodore Eigenmann, May 12, 1909 (Box 3)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Adele Eigenmann, circa 1909-1910(?) (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to daughters, circa 1909-1910(?) (Box 3)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, March 26, 1910 (Box 3)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, April 2, 1910 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Ulysses H. Smith, June 13, 1910 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann and Carl H. Eigenmann with Norman Eugene McIndoo, June 7-27, 1910; 3 Items (Box 3)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, July 10, 1910 (Box 3)
  - Lucretia Smith to Adele Eigenmann, September 1, 1910 (Box 3)
  - William Trelease, Missouri Botanical Garden, to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, September 6, 1910 (Box 3)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, September 7, 1910 (Box 3)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, 1910 (Box 3)
  - W. J. Holland, Carnegie Museum, to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, January 9, 1911 (Box 4)
  - John R. Berry to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, May 11, 1911 (Box 4)
  - Mary S. Berry to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, May 11, 1911 (Box 4)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Mary S. Berry, May 16, 1911 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Ana C. Smith(?), May 16, 1911 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, May 16, 1911 (Box 4)
  - Mary S. Berry to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, May 17, 1911 (Box 4)
  - C. K. Smith (brother) to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, May 20, 1911 (Box 4)
  - Theodore Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, August 3, 1911 (Box 4)
  - Theodore Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, August 17, 1911 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, September 4, 1911 (Box 4)
  - C.K. Smith Jr. to J. Russell Smith, October 30, 1911 (Box 4)
  - Silas Reed Smith to J. Russell Smith, November 27, 1911 (Box 4)
  - Nestor Young to J. Russell Smith, December 1, 1911 (Box 4)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to William Lowe Bryan, April 2, 1912 (Box 4)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to William Lowe Bryan, April 3, 1912 (Box 4)
  - Johnsonton-Slocum Company to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, June 9, 1912 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, June 26, 1913 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, July 5, 1913 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, July 13, 1913 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, July 23, 1913 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, July 25, 1913 (Box 4)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, July 28, 1913 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, July 30, 1913 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, circa July 1913 (Box 4)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Adele Eigenmann, 1913 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, August 6, 1914 (Box 4)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to daughters, September 9, 1914 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, September 18, 1914 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, April 22, 1915 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, May 2, 1915 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, May 29, 1915 (Box 4)
  - J. Russell Smith to unknown, July 26, 1915 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, September 1, 1915 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, September 12, 1915 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, September 23-24, 1915 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, October 2, 1915 (Box 4)
  - C. Heller to J. Russell Smith, October 6, 1915 (Box 4)
  - J. Russell Smith to C. Heller, October 8, 1915 (Box 4)
  - C. Heller to J. Russell Smith, October 11, 1915 (Box 4)
  - C. Heller to J. Russell Smith, November 18, 1915 (Box 4)
  - Charlotte Eigenmann to siblings, December 31, 1915 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, circa 1915? (Box 4)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Thora Eigenmann, April 21(?), 1916 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to "Peggy", March 4, 1916 (Box 4)
  - Charlotte Eigenmann to Adele Eigenmann, June 3, 1916 (Box 4)
  - J. Russell Smith to the Deputy Fire Marshal, City of San Diego, June 30, 1916 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, August 6, 1916 (Box 4)
  - John S. Chambers to J. Russell Smith, November 11, 1916 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, circa 1916-1917? (Box 4)
  - J. Russell Smith(?) to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, circa 1916-1917(?) (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, August 17, 1917 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, August 17, 1917 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, circa 1917? (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, circa 1917? (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, February 11, 1918 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, March 6, 1918 (Box 4)
  - Mary S. Berry to J. Russell Smith, September 7, 1918 (Box 4)
  - Tobias Dantzig to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, October 9, 1918 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Anita Muhl, December 25, 1918 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Adele Eigenmann, circa 1918 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, circa 1918-1919 (Box 4)
  - Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann to Adele Eigenmannn, August 20, 1919 (Box 4)
  - Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann to daughters, September 23, 1919 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Adele Eigenmann, September 30, 1919 (Box 4)
  - Thora Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, November 24, 1919 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Bertha B. Haynes (with note from Rosa Smith Eigenmann), December 17, 1919 (Box 4)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Thora Eigenmann, May 8, 1920 (Box 4)
  - Margaret Eigenmann to Adele and Thora Eigenmann, May 9, 1920 (Box 4)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Adele Eigenmann, May 9, 1920 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to children, August 14, 1920 (Box 4)
  - David Starr Jordan to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, August 19, 1920 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, November 14, 1920 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Thora Eigenmann, circa 1920 (Box 4)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, August 4, 1921 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, January 15, 1922 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, February 3, 1922 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to "Peg", February 7, 1922 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to "Snoot", June 12, 1922 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to family, July 5, 1922 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to family, July 17, 1922 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to family, July 26, 1922 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to family, circa 1922 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to "Peggy", February 1, 1923 (Box 4)
  - "Snoot" to "Snickerdoodle", April 9, 1923(?) (Box 4)
  - "Plucky Duck" to "Snoot", April 13, 1923 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, May 15, 1923 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, May 25, 1923 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to "Peg", August 6, 1923 (Box 4)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Mary S. Berry, October 14, 1923 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, October 19, 1923 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Thora Eigenmann, October 25, 1923 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, November 10, 1923 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to family, December 15, 1923 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, December 19, 1923 (Box 4)
  - Children's Hospital (San Francisco) to Adele Eigenmann, circa 1923 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to "Peggy", January 2, 1924 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, January 7, 1924 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, January 25, 1924 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, February 12, 1924 (Box 4)
  - John Eiler to Carl H. Eigenmann, February 28, 1924 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, March 7, 1924; 2 letters (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, March 10, 1924 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, March 22, 1924 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, April 18, 1924 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Charlotte Eigenmann, April 27, 1924 (Box 4)
  - John Eiler to Carl H. Eigenmann, May 19, 1924 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, June 1, 1924 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Charlotte Eigenmann, June 12, 1924 (Box 4)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, July 7, 1924 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to family, July 28, 1924 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to "Snoot", August 21, 1924 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to "Snoot", August 25, 1924 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, September 15, 1924 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to "Peggy", September 22, 1924 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to "Snoot", September 22, 1924(?) (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, September 23, 1924 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, October 7, 1924 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, December 2, 1924 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, December 30, 1924 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, circa 1924 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, circa 1924 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, circa 1924 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, Carl H. Eigenmann, and "Peg", circa 1924 (Box 5)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, January 25, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, January 25, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, March 6, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, March 23, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, April 7, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, May 10, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, May 22, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Charlotte Eigenmann, July 30, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, August 14, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to "Peg", September 6, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, October 10, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, October 13, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, October 14, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, November 12, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Mina B. Brush to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, December 16, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Adele Eigenmann to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, circa October, 1925 (Box 5)
  - Worth(?) Brehm to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, February 25, 1926 (Box 5)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to William Lowe Bryan, March 23, 1926 (Box 5)
  - Fernandus Payne to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, June 17, 1926 (Box 5)
  - Carl L. Hubbs (Museum of Zoology, University of Michigan) to Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann, July 14, 1926 (Box 5)
  - Charlotte Lowe Bryan to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, July 16, 1926 (Box 5)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to William Lowe Bryan, September 27, 1926 (Box 5)
  - William Lowe Bryan to Carl H. Eigenmann, November 2, 1926 (Box 5)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to William Lowe Bryan, November 19, 1926 (Box 5)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to "Etta"(?), December 4, 1926 (Box 5)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, circa 1926-1927(?) (Box 5)
  - Charlotte Lowe Bryan to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, January 15, 1927 (Box 5)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann with Indiana University Bursar's Office, February 13-19, 1927 (Box 5)
  - Fernandus Payne to Thora Eigenmann, February 15, 1927 (Box 5)
  - Barton Warren Evermann to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, March 31, 1927 (Box 5)
  - William Lowe Bryan to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, April 2, 1927 (Box 5)
  - William Lowe Bryan to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, May 2, 1927 (Box 5)
  - William Lowe Bryan to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, May 9, 1927 (Box 5)
  - William Lowe Bryan to Thora Eigenmann, May 9, 1927 (Box 5)
  - George Derby, National Cyclopedia of American Biography, to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, May 17, 1927 (Box 5)
  - William Lowe Bryan to Thora Eigenmann, May 19, 1927 (Box 5)
  - Charlotte Lowe Bryan to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, May 23, 1927 (Box 5)
  - William Lowe Bryan to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, May 27, 1927 (Box 5)
  - Clyde Furst to William Lowe Bryan, May 31, 1927 (Box 5)
  - William Lowe Bryan to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, June 4, 1927 (Box 5)
  - Laura Clark Hubbs to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, July 31, 1927 (Box 5)
  - Carl L. Hubbs, Museum of Zoology, University of Michigan, to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, October 7, 1927 (Box 5)
  - Carl L. Hubbs, Museum of Zoology, University of Michigan, to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, October 28, 1927 (Box 5)
  - Fernandus Payne to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, December 5, 1927 (Box 5)
  - Fernandus Payne to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, December 16, 1927 (Box 5)
  - Carl L. Hubbs, Museum of Zoology, University of Michigan, to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, January 4, 1928 (Box 5)
  - E.W. Gudger to Thora Eigenmann, January 9, 1928 (Box 5)
  - W. R. Allen? to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, February 13, 1928 (Box 5)
  - Thora Eigenmann(?) to W. R. Allen, February 18, 1928 (Box 5)
  - Thora Eigenmann to family, March 16, 1928 (Box 5)
  - Thora Eigenmann to Miss McNutt, August 27, 1928 (Box 5)
  - William Lowe Bryan to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, September 21, 1928 (Box 5)
  - Paul V. McNutt to Thora Eigenmann, November 22, 1928 (Box 5)
  - Laura Clark Hubbs to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, June 5, 1930 (Box 5)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Ivy Chamness (IU Alumni Quarterly), July 29, 1930 (Box 5)
  - Thora Eigenmann to San Diego Union re: Rosa Smith Eigenmann, June 26, 1941 (Box 5)
  - Mary Smith Berry to Rosa Smith Eigenmann, April 15, year unknown (Box 5)
  - Rosa Smith Eigenmann to Carl H. Eigenmann, July 21, year unknown (Box 5)
  - Carl H. Eigenmann to family, undated (Box 5)
  - Rosa Smith and Carl H. Eigenmann to unknown, undated (Box 5)
- Research, 1880, undated
  - Description of a scaly Blemmy found in algae lined tide pools, Pacific ocean, San Diego Co., CA, March 6, 1880 (Box 5)
  - On the Occurrence of a Species of Cremnobates at San Diego, CA, April 1880? (Box 5)
  - Lecture or article about rays of the San Diego Bay, undated (Box 5)
- Ephemera, 1880-1951; undated
  - Pacific Coast Steamship Company, Timetable, 1880 (Box 5)
  - Athenian Society Anniversary Invitation, 1881 (Box 5)
  - Specimen gift receipts, Smithsonian Institution, 1885-1886 (Box 5)
  - Commencement Invitation, 1886 (Box 5)
  - Newspaper clipping regarding the 64th anniversary of Mr. and Mrs. C.K. Smith, July 7, 1899 (Box 5)
  - Hinkle and Souders East Side Meat Market account statement, 1910s (Box 5)
  - J. Russell Smith receipts, 1910s (Box 5)
  - Loose, unsorted envelopes, circa 1911-1925 (Box 5)
    Scope and Contents
    Some envelopes contain writings from correspondents.
  - Adele Eigenmann medical school notes, 1919 (Box 5)
  - Unsorted clippings, circa 1920s (Box 5)
  - Who's Who vol. 25, Geographical Index, 1948-1949 (Box 5)
  - Mary Smith Berry genealogical materials, circa 1951 (Box 5)
  - Prescription written by Adele M. Eiler, M.D., for Rosa Smith and Carl Eigenmann for "California sunshine", September 23, year unknown (Box 5)
  - Flowers, undated (Box 5)